  1, Fill Time, MS
  2, Total Shot Time, MS
  3, Slow Shot Time, MS
  4, Fast Shot Time, MS
  5, Fast Shot Rise Time, MS
  6, Cycle Time, SEC
  7, User Time Int One, MS
  8, User Time Int Two, MS
  9, User Time Int Three, MS
 10, User Time Int Four, MS
 11, User Time Int Five, MS
 12, Biscuit Size, MM
 13, Calc Start Fast Shot, MM
 14, Intensification Pressure, BAR
 15, Intensification Rise Time, MS
 16, Eff Peak Intensification, BAR
 17, Impact Pressure to Peak, BAR
 18, Intens Squeeze Distance, MM
 19, Sleeve Full Velocity, MPS
 20, Runner Full Velocity, MPS
 21, Average Fill Velocity, MPS
 22, User Velocity Pos One, MPS
 23, User Velocity Pos Two, MPS
 24, User Velocity Pos Three, MPS
 25, User Velocity Pos Four, MPS
 26, User Avg Vel Range One, MPS
 27, User Avg Vel Range Two, MPS
 28, User Avg Vel Range Three, MPS
 29, User Avg Vel Range Four, MPS
 30, Position P1, MM
 31, Position P2, MM
 32, Position P3, MM
 33, Avg Slow Shot Velocity, MPS
 34, Avg Fast Show Velocity, MPS
 35, Fast Shot Distance, MM, MPS
